### Contact

84 Stanavage Rd Colchester CT 860-334-7613 (Mobile) gptdavenelson@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ davenelsongpt (LinkedIn) benhance.com (Company)

### Top Skills

User Experience (UX)
User Interface Design
User Experience Testing

# **Dave Nelson**

Web Developer at UnitedHealth Group Colchester

## Summary

Experienced User Experience Designer with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in User Experience Testing, Scrum, User Experience (UX), Audio Editing, and Agile Methodologies. Strong arts and design professional with a Master's Degree focused in Entertainment Business from Full Sail University.

## Experience

UnitedHealth Group UX/UI Designer October 2014 - Present (6 years) Hartford, CT

#### HealthSafe ID

Working in a reporting and design capacity understanding how users interact with an enterprise wide consumer identification system that supports 7.1 million users. Following day to day metrics in regards to registration, login, and authentication. Worked to understand where users pain points were based on the data of their interactions and then worked to adjust those pain points. Worked on a redesign of support call center administrative tool with focus on streamlining the call center users workflow.

#### **EOD Studios**

Studio Manager/Recording Engineer January 2014 - October 2014 (10 months) Colchester, CT

Operated a small, self-owned studio. Recorded and produced multiple projects of a wide genre variety.

### Education

Full Sail University

Master's Degree, Entertainment Business · (2012 - 2013)

# Full Sail University

Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Record Arts · (2010 - 2012)